const data = [
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "The word they in paragraph 1 refers to ________.",
    A: "people",
    B: "cities",
    C: "parks",
    D: "sports",
    Correct: "C. parks",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "According to paragraph 2,  how do parks help people in cities?",
    A: "Plants in the parks emit carbon dioxide that is needed for people to breathe.",
    B: "Trees in the parks release the sunâ€™s heat more quickly than building materials.",
    C: "Parks make cities warmer than than surrounding rural areas.",
    D: "Plants in the parks absorb a pollutant and emit oxygen for people to breathe.",
    Correct:
      "D. Plants in the parks absorb a pollutant and emit oxygen for people to breathe.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "Which of the following is NOT a building materials?",
    A: "oxygen",
    B: "metal",
    C: "concrete",
    D: "asphalt",
    Correct: "A. oxygen",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "The word mitigate in paragraph 2 is closest in meaning to _______.",
    A: "increase",
    B: "reduce",
    C: "allow",
    D: "save",
    Correct: "B. reduce",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "According to the author, one advantage that rooftop gardens have over parks is that they ________.",
    A: "decrease the Urban Heat Island Effect",
    B: "refresh the air with nourishing oxygen",
    C: "do not require the use of valuable urban land",
    D: "are less expensive than traditional park spaces",
    Correct: "C. do not require the use of valuable urban land",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "The word others in paragraph 3 refers to _______.",
    A: "gardens",
    B: "human beings",
    C: "rooftops",
    D: "hours of work",
    Correct: "A. gardens",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 3, when did people begin to create rooftop gardens?",
    A: "some years ago",
    B: "some decades ago",
    C: "some centuries ago",
    D: "thousands of years ago",
    Correct: "D. thousands of years ago",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 4, what can rooftop gardens do to reduce heating bills?",
    A: "They hold in heat in buildings.",
    B: "They prevent building absorbing heat.",
    C: "They replace carbon dioxide.",
    D: "They provide vegetables and herbs.",
    Correct: "A. They hold in heat in buildings.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "The author claims all of the following to be the benefits of rooftop gardens EXCEPT ________.",
    A: "beautiful decoration for houses",
    B: "savings on cooling bills",
    C: "better food for city dwellers",
    D: "improved air quality",
    Correct: "A. beautiful decoration for houses",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 3 and 4, which of the following best describes the main difference between parks and rooftop gardens?",
    A: "Parks are expensive to create while rooftop gardens are not.",
    B: "Parks are public while rooftop gardens are private.",
    C: "Parks absorb heat while rooftop gardens do not.",
    D: "Parks require much space while rooftop gardens do not.",
    Correct: "D. Parks require much space while rooftop gardens do not.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "What is the main topic of this passage?",
    A: "A language developed in the last few years",
    B: "One man’s efforts to create a universal language",
    C: "Using language to communicate internationally",
    D: "How language can be improved",
    Correct: "B. One man’s efforts to create a universal language",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "According to the passage, Zamenhof wanted to create a universal language ______.",
    A: "to provide a more complex language",
    B: "to create one world culture",
    C: "to resolve cultural differences",
    D: "to build a name for himself",
    Correct: "C. to resolve cultural differences",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "It can be inferred from the passage that the Esperanto word “malespera” means ______.",
    A: "hopelessness",
    B: "hopeless",
    C: "hope",
    D: "hopeful",
    Correct: "B. hopeless",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "The expression “popping up” in paragraph 4 could best be replaced by ______.",
    A: "hiding",
    B: "shouting",
    C: "leaping",
    D: "opening",
    Correct: "D. opening",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "It can be inferred from the passage that the Third World Congress of Esperanto took place in ______.",
    A: 1905,
    B: 1907,
    C: 1909,
    D: 1913,
    Correct: "B. 1907",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "According to the passage, what happened to the Tenth World Esperanto Congress?",
    A: "It was scheduled for 1915.",
    B: "It had attendees from 20 countries.",
    C: "It never took place.",
    D: "It had 4,000 attendees.",
    Correct: "C. It never took place.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "The expression “ups and downs” in paragraph 6 is closest in meaning to ______.",
    A: "takeoffs and landings",
    B: "floors and ceilings",
    C: "highs and lows",
    D: "tops and bottoms",
    Correct: "C. highs and lows",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "Which paragraph describes the predecessor to Esperanto?",
    A: "The first paragraph",
    B: "The second paragraph",
    C: "The third paragraph",
    D: "The fourth paragraph",
    Correct: "B. The second paragraph",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "The passage would most likely be assigned reading in a course on ______.",
    A: "applied linguistics",
    B: "European history",
    C: "English grammar",
    D: "world government",
    Correct: "A. applied linguistics",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "The paragraph following the passage most likely discusses ______.",
    A: "another of Zamenhof’s accomplishments",
    B: "attempts to reconvene the World Congress of Esperanto in the 1920s",
    C: "the disadvantages of using an artificial language",
    D: "how current supporters of Esperanto are encouraging its growth",
    Correct:
      "D. how current supporters of Esperanto are encouraging its growth",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "Which of the following is true about the extreme weather events?",
    A: "They have an influence on the climate.",
    B: "They kill more people than before.",
    C: "They cause mud slides in Bangkok.",
    D: "They are part of a long-term change.",
    Correct: "D. They are part of a long-term change.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "According to paragraph 2 of the article, _________.",
    A: "scientists don’t know what causes extreme weather.",
    B: "there’s more than one factor influencing our weather.",
    C: "it’s not possible for humans to influence the weather.",
    D: "big storms, such as hurricanes and typhoons, come from the oceans.",
    Correct: "B. there’s more than one factor influencing our weather.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "Why was the rain in Nashville considered to be an extreme event?",
    A: "There was very high rainfall over many days.",
    B: "The amount of rain was forecast in advance.",
    C: "There was very high rainfall in a very short time.",
    D: "The amount of rain was unmeasurable.",
    Correct: "C. There was very high rainfall in a very short time.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "Which of the following is true about the rainfall in Nashville in May 2010?",
    A: "It caused very rare flooding.",
    B: "It last happened a thousand years ago.",
    C: "It happens every one hundred years.",
    D: "It was more frequent in the past.",
    Correct: "A. It caused very rare flooding.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "What caused deaths in Rio de Janeiro?",
    A: "People were trapped under soil",
    B: "The intensity of the rain",
    C: "Extensive floods",
    D: "The yearly mud slides",
    Correct: "A. People were trapped under soil",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "According to the article, __________.",
    A: "there has been a dramatic increase in the economic costs of extreme weather",
    B: "extreme weather events have risen by 25 percent since 2010",
    C: "in 2011, 25 percent of financial losses were weather-related",
    D: "the under-watered factories manufacture computer hard drives",
    Correct: "C. in 2011, 25 percent of financial losses were weather-related",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "Which statement is NOT supported by information in the article?",
    A: "Extreme weather is influenced by human activity.",
    B: "Unusual weather events are part of natural weather cycles.",
    C: "In the world, there are two weather cycles affect weather patterns worldwide",
    D: "Such extreme weather is too rare to be a result of climate change.",
    Correct:
      "D. Such extreme weather is too rare to be a result of climate change.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "What is the key factor in the formation of storms?",
    A: "warmer land temperatures",
    B: "greenhouse gases",
    C: "moisture in the air",
    D: "the heat released by air-conditioners",
    Correct: "C. moisture in the air",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "Why did fewer people die in France in the 2006 heat wave?",
    A: "There were better facilities provided.",
    B: "Fewer people were in city centers at the time.",
    C: "It wasn’t as severe as in 2003.",
    D: "People didn’t go out when it was too hot.",
    Correct: "A. There were better facilities provided.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "According to Michael Oppenheimer, what should people do?",
    A: "There’s no way to stop extreme weather.",
    B: "We can be better prepared for the effects of climate change.",
    C: "We need to spend more money so that fewer people die.",
    D: "We need to provide citizens with air conditioners during hottest periods.",
    Correct: "B. We can be better prepared for the effects of climate change.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "According to the passage, sailors 4,000 years ago _______.",
    A: "were able to calculate their speed",
    B: "were dependent on stars to tell time",
    C: "never ventured away from the coastline",
    D: "used the compass to navigate",
    Correct: "A. were able to calculate their speed",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "The word rudimentary in paragraph 1 is closest in meaning to _______.",
    A: "reliable",
    B: "direct",
    C: "established",
    D: "elementary",
    Correct: "D. elementary",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "The word it in paragraph 2 refers to ________.",
    A: "premise",
    B: "compass",
    C: "needle",
    D: "pivot",
    Correct: "C. needle",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "It is NOT stated in the passage that the astrolabe _______.",
    A: "could determine distance from the equator",
    B: "was similar in shape to a sundial",
    C: "had moving parts",
    D: "was a circular – shaped device",
    Correct: "B. was similar in shape to a sundial",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "The word rule as used in paragraph 3 is most likely _______.",
    A: "a regular followed by sailors on a ship",
    B: "a law enacted by a government",
    C: "a device used to make measurements",
    D: "a customary way of acting",
    Correct: "C. a device used to make measurements",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "The author refers to the missing piece of the navigational puzzle in paragraph 4 in order to ________.",
    A: "show that navigation was considered as amusing game",
    B: "highlight that how to determine longitude was the final problem to be solved",
    C: "indicate that missing ships were difficult to find",
    D: "determine that it was difficult to calculate latitude",
    Correct:
      "B. highlight that how to determine longitude was the final problem to be solved",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "Look at the four square [ ] that indicate where the following sentence could be added to the last paragraph. 'Though many tried, it took a number of years after the offer was made for someone to succeed.' Where could the sentence best be added?",
    A: "[A]",
    B: "[B]",
    C: "[C]",
    D: "[D]",
    Correct: "B. [B]",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "Which of the following is NOT a device to determine latitude?",
    A: "chronometer",
    B: "sextant",
    C: "backstaff",
    D: "sundial",
    Correct: "A. chronometer",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question:
      "Which of the sentences below best expresses the essential information in the highlighted sentence in paragraph 4?",
    A: "A chronometer could be used to measure longitude by combining knowledge about the rising Sun and accurate measurement of time.",
    B: "A chronometer could be used to determine when the Sun was going to rise.",
    C: "A chronometer could be used only to calculate longitude if one was traveling in a westerly direction.",
    D: "A chronometer was an inaccurate measure of time because of the movement of the ship.",
    Correct:
      "A. A chronometer could be used to measure longitude by combining knowledge about the rising Sun and accurate measurement of time.",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE1",
    Question: "It is implied in the passage that _______.",
    A: "Harrison’s device was not very accurate",
    B: "Harrison spent considerable time travelling",
    C: "Harrison received 20,000 pounds from Parliament",
    D: "Harrison’s device was the best in determining latitude",
    Correct: "C. Harrison received 20,000 pounds from Parliament",
  },
  {
    CODE: "",
    Question: "",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "",
    Question: "",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "",
    Question: "",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "The Association of Southeast Asian Nations ________.",
    A: "consists of some Western nations",
    B: "was established by the Philippines",
    C: "was founded on 8 August 1967",
    D: "was established by Thailand",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "How many countries did ASEAN first consist of?",
    A: "Five",
    B: "Seven",
    C: "Eight",
    D: "Ten",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "The pronoun it in the first paragraph refers to ________.",
    A: "the Association of Southeast Asian Nations",
    B: "the most successful inter-governmental organization",
    C: "Bangkok",
    D: "the ASEAN Declaration",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "What is the purpose of the declaration?",
    A: "To show that Southeast Asia is independent",
    B: "To show the difference between southeast and northeast Asian nations",
    C: "To mark the birth of ASEAN and its aims and purposes",
    D: "To develop the economy of the whole Asia",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Which does not belong to the purpose and aim of the Association of Southeast Asian Nations?",
    A: "friendship",
    B: "destruction",
    C: "creation",
    D: "cooperation",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "What does the word cooperation in paragraph 2 mean?",
    A: "collaboration",
    B: "union",
    C: "federation",
    D: "society",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "In which field DON’T the members of ASEAN cooperate in?",
    A: "techniques",
    B: "society",
    C: "culture",
    D: "linguistics",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "What do the sheaves in the ASEAN logo represent?",
    A: "the number of its members",
    B: "the spirit of cordiality",
    C: "the purposes of ASEAN",
    D: "the strength of ASEAN",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "Up to 1997, how many countries were there in ASEAN?",
    A: 5,
    B: 6,
    C: 8,
    D: 10,
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "The word original in paragraph 3 means ________.",
    A: "new and interesting",
    B: "first",
    C: "authentic",
    D: "first-hand",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Which of the following is the best definition of a civilization?",
    A: "Neolithic towns and cities",
    B: "Types of complex cultures",
    C: "An agricultural community",
    D: "Large population centers",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "The word “its” in paragraph 1 refers to_______.",
    A: "copper’s",
    B: "metal’s",
    C: "iron’s",
    D: "bronze’s",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 2, what happens as societies become more prosperous?",
    A: "More goods are produced.",
    B: "Walled cities are built.",
    C: "Laws are instituted.",
    D: "The size of families increased.",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "The word “hardly” in paragraph 2 is closest in meaning to_______.",
    A: "frequently",
    B: "likely",
    C: "barely",
    D: "obviously",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "Why does the author mention Neolithic towns in paragraph 2?",
    A: "To give an example of a civilization",
    B: "To explain the invention of writing systems",
    C: "To argue that they should be classified as villages",
    D: "To contrast them with the civilizations that evolved",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "According to paragraph 3, how was the class system structured?",
    A: "An upper class and a lower class",
    B: "Slaves, free people, and a ruling class",
    C: "A king, an army, and slaves",
    D: "Intellectuals and uneducated farmers and workers",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Which of the sentences below best expresses the information in the following statement? Historians have identified a number of basic characteristics of civilization, most of which are; evident in the Mesopotamian and Egyptian civilizations.",
    A: "Mesopotamian and Egyptian civilizations exhibit the majority of the characteristics identified by historians.",
    B: "The characteristics that historians have identified are not found in the Egyptian and Mesopotamian cultures.",
    C: "Civilizations in Mesopotamia and Egypt were identified by historians who were studying the characteristics of early cultures.",
    D: "The identification of most historical civilizations includes either Egypt or Mesopotamia on the list.",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "The word “crucial” in paragraph 3 is closest in meaning to_______.",
    A: "fundamental",
    B: "arbitrary",
    C: "disruptive",
    D: "suitable",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "The word “prominent” in paragraph 3 is closest in meaning to_______.",
    A: "weak",
    B: "important",
    C: "artistic",
    D: "intellectual",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 4, how can the independent development of civilization in different geographic regions be explained?",
    A: "Scholars agree that food surpluses encouraged populations to be concentrated in certain areas.",
    B: "There are several theories that explain the rise of civilization in the ancient world.",
    C: "The model of civilization was probably carried from one region to another along trade routes.",
    D: "Historians attribute the emergence of early cities at about the same time as a coincidence.",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "What can be inferred about the waste dumped into the world’s oceans?",
    A: "It’s mainly household waste",
    B: "Much of it was not treated",
    C: "It is billions of tons",
    D: "It is primary industrial waste",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "As can be inferred from the passage, which of the following was NOT disposed into the ocean?",
    A: "waste from dead plants",
    B: "waste from cruise ships",
    C: "wastewater sludge",
    D: "radioactive waste",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Which of the following is NOT referred to as use of hydrological cycle?",
    A: "refreshing the land",
    B: "separating water from used liquid",
    C: "cleaning water",
    D: "renewing the water supply",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Which of the following has similar meaning to the word “contaminants” in the second paragraph?",
    A: "pollutants",
    B: "rushes",
    C: "sea water",
    D: "vapor",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "What does the word “which” in the second paragraph refer to?",
    A: "rain water",
    B: "the earth",
    C: "sea water",
    D: "water vaporizer",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Why are chemicals, petroleum products and radioactive materials mentioned in the passage?",
    A: "as untreated waste",
    B: "as industrial substances",
    C: "as raw sewage",
    D: "as dangerous pollutants",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Which of the following is NOT referred to as a result of polluted ocean water?",
    A: "killing fish",
    B: "harming people who eat sea food",
    C: "spoiling beach beauty",
    D: "killing shore birds",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "Which of the following is NOT an example of farming runoff?",
    A: "manure",
    B: "pesticide",
    C: "road salt",
    D: "fertilizer",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "Which of the following can be inferred from the passage?",
    A: "It is expensive to build waste treatment plants.",
    B: "Developing countries do not need waste treatment plant yet.",
    C: "The environment of developed countries is more polluted than that of poor countries.",
    D: "The environment of industrial countries is more polluted than that of agricultural countries.",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "Where is the passage most probably found?",
    A: "in a geography book",
    B: "in a bibliography",
    C: "in a tourism book",
    D: "in a social science report",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "The author includes the last sentence in paragraph 1 in order to _______.",
    A: "describe events leading up to the events in the following paragraphs",
    B: "provide examples for many different types of silent films",
    C: "announce the organization of the passage",
    D: "present a concluding idea to summarize paragraph 1",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "It is implied in paragraph 2 that _______.",
    A: "the Kinetoscope was invented some time before the Kinetograph",
    B: "the Kinetoscope was used to view films created with the Kinetograph",
    C: "the Cinematographe could create films but could not be used to view them",
    D: "the Cinematographe was used to view films created with the Kinetosgraph",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "The word turned in paragraph 2 could best be replaced by ________.",
    A: "rotated",
    B: "accepted",
    C: "changed",
    D: "alternated",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Look at the four squares [ ] that indicate where the following sentence could be added to paragraph 2. 'They depicted short everyday scenes of people taking part in outdoor activities, laborers working at a construction site, and travelers scurrying through a train station.' Where could the sentence best be added?",
    A: "[A]",
    B: "[B]",
    C: "[C]",
    D: "[D]",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "Films made from 1908 to 1917 ________.",
    A: "were more rudimentary than previous films",
    B: "reflected fewer topics",
    C: "had actors with a lot of words",
    D: "were reviewed on newspapers",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "The word repertoire in paragraph 3 could best be replaced by ________.",
    A: "range",
    B: "basis",
    C: "center",
    D: "success",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "The word them in paragraph 4 refers to ________.",
    A: "early decades",
    B: "early devices",
    C: "sound quality and amplification",
    D: "studios",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "The phrase took a chance in paragraph 4 is closest in meaning to",
    A: "behaved randomly",
    B: "lost an opportunity",
    C: "took a risk",
    D: "had good fortune",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question: "According to paragraph 4, The Jazz Singer ________.",
    A: "was produced by Fox Studios",
    B: "was the last great silent film",
    C: "was about the life of Al Johnson",
    D: "was extremely successful",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 2",
    Question:
      "Which of the sentences below best expresses the essential information in the highlighted sentence in paragraph 4?",
    A: "After studios were sure that pictures with sound were going to be successful, they converted to talking pictures relatively quickly",
    B: "The future of film was presented in a series of talking films that were produced in Hollywood for release in 1929",
    C: "The era of silent films ended when the exclusive production for making talking pictures was granted to Hollywood studios.",
    D: "It was clear to studios that talking pictures were only a fad, so they decided not to produce them until sometime in the future.",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "",
    Question: "",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "",
    Question: "",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "How many Chinese men start to smoke before the age of 20?",
    A: "one-third",
    B: "two-thirds",
    C: "half",
    D: "all of them",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What does the word “those men” in paragraph 2 refer to?",
    A: "Men who smoke under the age of 20",
    B: "Men who smoke above the age of 20",
    C: "Men who give up smoking",
    D: "Men who smoke in public",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "By 2030, how many men in China may die from smoking every year?",
    A: "one million",
    B: "two million",
    C: "three million",
    D: "four million",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "In many areas of China, when do men usually smoke?",
    A: "Before a meal",
    B: "After a meal",
    C: "Before they go to sleep",
    D: "When they get up",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "According to WHO, only_______ of Chinese adults can list bad effects of smoking.",
    A: "one-third",
    B: "one-fourth",
    C: "one-fifth",
    D: "a half",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "“Beijing” refers to",
    A: "China",
    B: "The city of Beijing",
    C: "The Chinese government",
    D: "People who live in Beijing",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What is Richard Peto’s attitude toward smoking in China?",
    A: "He doesn’t believe that people will give up smoking",
    B: "He is disappointed with the Chinese government.",
    C: "He thinks that people possibly stop smoking if they see reasons.",
    D: "He is sure about the rise of future deaths in China.",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "Which of the following words does the word “hamper” have closest meaning to?",
    A: "basket",
    B: "assist",
    C: "prohibit",
    D: "restrict",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What is the writer’s purpose?",
    A: "To argue over smoking policy in China",
    B: "To support smoking in China",
    C: "To warn and prevent smoking in China",
    D: "To report the result of a research paper",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What does the writer imply about Chinese government?",
    A: "They do not want to stop people from smoking.",
    B: "They have tried to stop people from smoking in public but with little success.",
    C: "They have tried to close tobacco companies.",
    D: "They do not care about smoking.",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "The word “we” in paragraph 2 refers to",
    A: "humans",
    B: "economists, sociologists, and politicians",
    C: "animals",
    D: "scientists",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 2, how many degrees could the Earth warm up?",
    A: "2,5",
    B: "2.5 or 10",
    C: 10,
    D: "from 2.5 to 10",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 3, why should we stabilize GHG concentrations around 450-550 parts per million?",
    A: "to avoid the most serious effects of climate change",
    B: "to avoid all damaging impacts of climate change",
    C: "to mend the most damaging impacts of climate change",
    D: "to stop climate change",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What does “which” in paragraph 3 refer to?",
    A: "current concentrations",
    B: "that current concentrations are about 380 ppm",
    C: "380 ppm",
    D: "ppm",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "Why does the author mention Stephen Pacala and Robert Socolow?",
    A: "To introduce two researchers in the field",
    B: "To proves that researchers are working to reduce GHG emission",
    C: "To introduce one way to reduce GHG emission",
    D: "To introduce Princeton University",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What stabilization wedges are NOT mentioned in the passage?",
    A: "create environment-friendly materials",
    B: "capture and store carbon dioxide underground",
    C: "increase the use of renewable energy",
    D: "grow more trees",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What does “them” refer to?",
    A: "researchers",
    B: "humans",
    C: "renewable resources",
    D: "wedges",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What is the best title for this passage?",
    A: "Arguments over Global Warming",
    B: "Global Warming and its Causes",
    C: "Global Warming Solutions",
    D: "Global Warming’s Effect on Earth",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "“Sequestering” has closest meaning to",
    A: "absorb",
    B: "isolate",
    C: "release",
    D: "emit",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "Why does the writer mention “drawbacks” in the last paragraph?",
    A: "To introduce the disadvantages of solutions in the following paragraph",
    B: "To emphasize the disadvantages of the solutions in the previous paragraph",
    C: "To recommend readers not to use the solutions",
    D: "To emphasize the advantages of the solutions in different contexts",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "According to paragraph 2, the process ofvisual perception",
    A: "A.is not the same for all people",
    B: "begins with patterns of light",
    C: "is not very scientific",
    D: "requires other senses to function",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What did Matisse reinterpret?",
    A: "A goddess from mythology",
    B: "A painting by another artist",
    C: "An ancient sculpture",
    D: "D.A man in history",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "The word “them” in the last paragraph refers to",
    A: "A.each attentive observer",
    B: "thoughts and emotions",
    C: "a lifetime ofexperiences",
    D: "great works of art",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "The word “bequeath” in the passage isclosest in meaning to",
    A: "A.make out",
    B: "pass on",
    C: "look over",
    D: "take in",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "The author mentions all of the followingways to enhance the appreciation of art EXCEPT",
    A: "A.understanding the artistic process",
    B: "becoming familiar with the history",
    C: "experiencing the art by copying",
    D: "knowing about the life of the artist",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What is the main topic of this passage?",
    A: "Visual perception of sensory material",
    B: "The historical context for artistic expression",
    C: "Studying Van Gogh's The Starry Night",
    D: "The appreciation of works of art",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "Which of the sentences below best expresses the information in the highlighted statement in the passage?",
    A: "A.We see images differently because ofthe mode of perception.",
    B: "Although we see images differently, the mode of perception is similar.",
    C: "Since the mode of perception is similar, we see images in the sameway.",
    D: "When the mode of perception is the same, we see the same images",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "Why might Van Gogh have painted The Starry Night?",
    A: "To symbolize the journey of life afterdeath",
    B: "To create a dramatic contrast with thesky",
    C: "To place a strong image in theforeground",
    D: "To include nature from his earlyexperience",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "The word “intrigued” in the passage isclosest in meaning to",
    A: "A.very pleased",
    B: "very confused",
    C: "very interested",
    D: "very surprised",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "What can be inferred from the last paragraph?",
    A: "Greatest artworks are impossible to understand.",
    B: "The author shows negative feelings toward contemporary art.",
    C: "People need knowledge to understand art.",
    D: "D.What we see in art is determined by our emotions, experiences, and thoughts.",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "How do antibiotics treat infections?",
    A: "They interfere with the reproductive cycle of bacteria.",
    B: "They construct cell walls to resist bacteria.",
    C: "They inject enzymes that explode in affected cells.",
    D: "They increase the mitosis of healthy cells",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "The word “them” in paragraph 4 refers to",
    A: "A.whatever properties",
    B: "resistant bacteria",
    C: "their competition",
    D: "those individuals",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "The word “anticipated” in the passage isclosest in meaning to",
    A: "A.predicted",
    B: "concealed",
    C: "investigated",
    D: "disregarded",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "Which of the following best expresses themain idea of this passage?",
    A: 'The "miracle drug" penicillin',
    B: "Drug-resistant bacteria",
    C: "C.Staphylococcus infections",
    D: "Gene therapy treatments",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 4, why do somebacteria benefit from antibiotics?",
    A: "The antibiotic eliminates competingbacteria, allowing resistant bacteria toreproduce.",
    B: "The resistant bacteria compete with theantibiotic, and the bacteria becomestronger.",
    C: "The competition helps the resistantbacteria to multiply by reproducingwith the resistant type.",
    D: "The properties of the antibiotic areacquired by the bacteria, making itresistant to the competition.",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "The word “complacency” in the passage isclosest in meaning to",
    A: "A.consensus of agreement",
    B: "fear of consequences",
    C: "lack ofconcern",
    D: "awareness of potential",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "Which of the sentences below bestexpresses the information in thehighlighted statement in the passage?",
    A: "Some antibiotics affect a population ofbacteria more efficiently than others.",
    B: "There are several reasons why some bacteria do not respond to most antibiotics.",
    C: "The effect ofantibiotics on bacteria is tobind them together into one population.",
    D: "A small number of bacteria in anysample will probably be resistant to aspecific antibiotic.",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "The author mentions all of the followingreasons for drug resistant bacteria to appear EXCEPT",
    A: "A.there was not enough profit incentivefor companies to continue developingnew antibiotics",
    B: "B.statistically, some drug-resistantbacteria will occur naturally in anylarge population ofbacteria",
    C: "C.the newer antibiotics were not asstrong and effective as the original penicillin-based drugs",
    D: "D.competing bacteria are destroyed by antibiotics, allowing resistant bacteria to prosper.",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question: "It can be inferred from the passage that",
    A: "research to develop new antibiotics will not be necessary in the future",
    B: "the scientific community was not surprised by the resistant strains of bacteria",
    C: "antibiotics are not very expensive when they are made available commercially",
    D: "it takes years for a new drug to be made available commercially for consumers",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 3",
    Question:
      "Which of the following statements is NOT a main idea of the passage?",
    A: "Many strains of bacteria have become resistant to the antibiotics currently available.",
    B: "B.Funding for the production of new antibiotics has been allocated to drug companies.",
    C: "The first antibiotics were very effective in blocking the reproduction of bacteria.",
    D: "New antibiotics are being developed to combat bacteria that resist the older antibiotics.",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "",
    Question: "",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "",
    Question: "",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "What is the main idea of the passage ?",
    A: "How Jonas Salk trained to be a physician and medical researcher",
    B: "How the medical research of Jonas Salk led to the development of the polio vaccine",
    C: "How Salk and his colleagues learned to kill viruses",
    D: "How Salk was promoted to important positions at the University of Pennsylvania",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which of the following is the closest in meaning to the underlined word “vaccine” as used in paragraph 1 of the passage ?",
    A: "Medicine designed to cure a disease temporarily",
    B: "Medicine that cures a disease after the patient gets sick",
    C: "Medicine designed to kill viruses that are fatal to children",
    D: "Medicine that creates immunity against a disease",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "In the first paragraph, what was Thomas Francis Jr. studying ?",
    A: "How to prevent the spread of influenza in Michigan",
    B: "How to work with physicians from Manhattan",
    C: "How to develop vaccines from killed viruses",
    D: "How to get a degree in medicine from New York University",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which sentence in the second paragraph describes Salk’s first work at the University of Pittsburg ?",
    A: "The first sentence",
    B: "The second sentence",
    C: "The third sentence",
    D: "None of the above",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which word is closest in meaning to the underlined word “corroborated” as used in paragraph 2 of the passage ?",
    A: "Rejected",
    B: "Published",
    C: "Examined",
    D: "Confirmed",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "All of the following statements about the killed virus vaccine are true EXCEPT :",
    A: "it did not induce antibody formation in monkeys",
    B: "it had three strains that scientiests worked with",
    C: "it was incapable of producing the disease",
    D: "it helped monkeys form antibodies",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The underlined word “findings” in paragraph 3 refers to",
    A: "Results",
    B: "Antibody levels",
    C: "Vaccine",
    D: "Polio",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "From the passage, it can be inferred that the experimental polio vaccine was given to people by",
    A: "pill",
    B: "injection",
    C: "surgery",
    D: "liquid",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "In the passage, it is implied that the Salk Institute was",
    A: "originally called the Institute for Biological Studies",
    B: "originally the University of Michigan School of Public Health",
    C: "originally the Virus Research Laboratory at the University of Pittsburg",
    D: "originally the medical school at New York University",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Where in the passage could the following sentence best fit? Thousands of children and adults were free from the fears of contracting this terrible disease",
    A: "At the end of paragraph 1",
    B: "At the end of paragraph 2",
    C: "At the end of paragraph 3",
    D: "At the end of paragraph 4",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which sentence in paragraph 1 explains who could go anywhere in the Forbidden City at any time ?",
    A: "Sentence 2",
    B: "Sentence 3",
    C: "Sentence 4",
    D: "Sentence 5",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "How long did it take to build the Forbidden City?",
    A: "About five years",
    B: "About seven years",
    C: "About ten years",
    D: "About fourteen years",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "From the passage, it can be inferred that",
    A: "Chinese architects borrowed ideas from many different countries",
    B: "the design of the Forbidden City is dull and colorless",
    C: "the architecture of the Forbidden City exemplifies traditional Chinese values",
    D: "the garden of the Forbidden City was laid out in a strict, rectangular pattern",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which phrase is closest in meaning to the underlined word “unparalleled” as used in paragraph 3?",
    A: "At an angle from the main line",
    B: "A high quality found nowhere else",
    C: "Partially designed in a foreign country",
    D: "Careless of small details in design",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which word(s) does the underlined word “its” refer to in paragraph 3?",
    A: "UNESCO",
    B: "Architecture",
    C: "Palace",
    D: "World Heritage List",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "From the passage, it is implied that the main entrance area to the Forbidden City is",
    A: "surrounded by three tall walls",
    B: "painted gold and green",
    C: "decorated with statuettes",
    D: "not very impressive",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which phrase is closest in meaning to the underlined word “proclamations” as used in paragraph 4?",
    A: "Music composed for public ceremonies",
    B: "Speeches encouraging soldiers to fight",
    C: "Official public announcements",
    D: "Poetry written for the emperor",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "All the following are found in the Imperial Garden EXCEPT:",
    A: "fishponds",
    B: "sculpture",
    C: "white marble bridges",
    D: "flowerbeds",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "According to the passage, what do the bridges over the Golden River lead to?",
    A: "The Meridian gate",
    B: "The center of Beijing",
    C: "The Gate of Supreme Harmony",
    D: "The Imperial Gardens",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which phrase is closest meaning to the underlined word “spontaneous” as used in paragraph 6?",
    A: "Without meaning",
    B: "Without thinking",
    C: "Without planning",
    D: "Without drawing",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The phrase “brought about” in paragraph 1 is closest in meaning to",
    A: "carried",
    B: "raised",
    C: "led",
    D: "caused",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The underlined word “those” in paragraph 2 refers to",
    A: "teeth",
    B: "casts",
    C: "brains",
    D: "archeologists",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The underlined word “predecessors” in paragraph 3 is closest in meaning to",
    A: "ancestors",
    B: "precedents",
    C: "survivors",
    D: "successors",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "It is NOT stated in the passage that Neanderthal tools were used to",
    A: "chop wood",
    B: "make woven clothing",
    C: "prepare things to eat",
    D: "prepare animal skins for use",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The underlined word “picture” in paragraph 4 could best be replaced by",
    A: "fantasy",
    B: "photograph",
    C: "conception",
    D: "sight",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The author refers to “cemeteries” in paragraph 4 in order to",
    A: "indicate that Neanderthals buried their dead as their predecessors had",
    B: "make a point about the use of Neanderthal tools in the construction of cemeteries",
    C: "demonstrate that Neanderthals were unsuccessful in their attempt to initiate social rituals",
    D: "provide an example of a Neanderthal social ritual",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The underlined word “proof” in paragraph 4 is closest in meaning to",
    A: "evidence",
    B: "motivation",
    C: "details",
    D: "logic",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which of the following is stated in the passage about Neanderthal burial sites ?",
    A: "They have all been found in only one place.",
    B: "They all seem to demonstrate the existence of Neanderthal social structure.",
    C: "They have all held the remains of old people",
    D: "They have all been surrounded by flowers.",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The underlined word “fit” in paragraph 4 could best be replaced by",
    A: "healthy",
    B: "appropriate",
    C: "necessary",
    D: "old",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "An “ibex” in paragraph 4 is most likely a type of",
    A: "clothing",
    B: "weapon",
    C: "animal",
    D: "gemstone",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "It can be inferred from the information in paragraph 1 that the theoretical decision-making process",
    A: "involves only the decision maker",
    B: "requires the contemplation of numerous options",
    C: "is made without the decision unit",
    D: "does not work in real situations",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The underlined phrase “in conjunction with” in paragraph 1could best be replaced by",
    A: "along with",
    B: "tied to",
    C: "apart from",
    D: "connected to",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "All of the following are listed in paragraph 1 as having an effect on decisions EXCEPT",
    A: "evaluation of the problem",
    B: "focus on objectives",
    C: "generation of options",
    D: "open-ended discussions",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The underlined word “eclectic” in paragraph 2 is closest in meaning to",
    A: "bizarre",
    B: "personal",
    C: "mixed",
    D: "organized",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "It can be inferred from paragraph 3 that a rational actor would be least likely to",
    A: "deal with a specific threat",
    B: "work in a random fashion",
    C: "ponder various options",
    D: "consider disadvantages of options",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The underlined word “it” in paragraph 3 refers to",
    A: "each option",
    B: "the best option",
    C: "careful analysis",
    D: "variation",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Why does the author mention a satisfier, one who selects the first satisfactory option rather than continuing the decision-making process until the optimal decision has been reached in paragraph 3 ?",
    A: "A satisfier shows contrasting behavior to a rational actor",
    B: "A satisfier exhibits more common behavior than a rational actor",
    C: "A satisfier is the predecessor of a rational actor",
    D: "A satisfier shares some characteristics with a rational actor",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The underlined word “places” in paragraph 4 could best be replaced by",
    A: "locates",
    B: "puts",
    C: "finds",
    D: "sets",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The underlined word “dynamics” in paragraph 5 is closest in meaning to",
    A: "explosions",
    B: "emotions",
    C: "philosophies",
    D: "interactions",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "According to paragraph 5, what is the end result of political bargaining within an organization?",
    A: "No decision is ever reached.",
    B: "Differing interests and motives are changed.",
    C: "No one is completely satisfied with the final outcome.",
    D: "The members of the decision unit leave the unit.",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "CODE 5",
    A: "",
    B: "",
    C: "",
    D: "",
    Correct: "",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "At this time of year______.",
    A: "the TV channels change all their programmes.",
    B: "the writer disappoints the TV channels with her reviews.",
    C: "the writer hopes for something that never happens.",
    D: "the writer's favourite programmes often disappear.",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "How does the writer describe the current programmes on SuperTV?",
    A: "exciting",
    B: "informative",
    C: "strange",
    D: "disappointing",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "What does 'They' in paragraph 1 refer to?",
    A: "SuperTV",
    B: "the TV channels",
    C: "the presenters of VJ-TV",
    D: "TV viewers",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The writer says that Staff Room will probably______.",
    A: "be successful.",
    B: "shock students.",
    C: "be worse than Train Driver.",
    D: "be on instead of Life in Aylesford Street.",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "Characters of the show Staff Room are______.",
    A: "students",
    B: "teachers",
    C: "travellers",
    D: "Channel 9's audience",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The word “hilarious” in paragraph 2 is closest in meaning to______.",
    A: "amusing",
    B: "informative",
    C: "strange",
    D: "up-to-date",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The writer thinks that Joke-a-Cola is now ______.",
    A: "more difficult to understand.",
    B: "more popular with viewers. 37",
    C: "funnier than before.",
    D: "more like a sitcom.",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "Because of the various choice of entertainment ______.",
    A: "people watch more television.",
    B: "people move to areas with more facilities.",
    C: "programme makers have to tell lies.",
    D: "programmes have to be more exciting.",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The writer thinks that television______.",
    A: "will never be as popular as the theatre is.",
    B: "should show more programmes about hobbies.",
    C: "could lose its popularity in the future.",
    D: "ought to provide more than just entertainment.",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which of the following channels would the author most probably recommend viewers to watch?",
    A: "SuperTV",
    B: "Channel 9",
    C: "BTV1",
    D: "all of them",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      'The word "romance" in paragraph 1 could be best replaced by _______.',
    A: "love affair",
    B: "fascination",
    C: "charm",
    D: "lover",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "Why did Ewan's relationship with his first girlfriend finish?",
    A: "She didn't enjoy walking.",
    B: "She met someone with a motorbike.",
    C: "He was upset by her behavior.",
    D: "He made her angry.",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "What does “such trivialities” in paragraph 2 refer to?",
    A: "his mother’s attitude to the bike",
    B: "the bike’s size and colour",
    C: "the bike’s price",
    D: "the bike’s quality and its manufacturer",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "Why didn't Ewan buy the bike immediately?",
    A: "He couldn't afford it.",
    B: "He wasn't old enough to ride it.",
    C: "He hadn't learnt how to ride it.",
    D: "He didn't know if his girlfriend would like it.",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The adults were frightened the first time Ewan rode a motorbike because they thought ______.",
    A: "the bike was too noisy",
    B: "the bike was too fast",
    C: "he was going to have an accident",
    D: "the bike was too big for him",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "What was Ewan's main reason for buying the motorbike?",
    A: "It was less expensive than a car.",
    B: "It would help his relationship with his girlfriend.",
    C: "It was good for his image.",
    D: "It was a useful means of transport.",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "How did Ewan’s desire for the bike affect his behaviour?",
    A: "He couldn’t think about anything else.",
    B: "He spent more time talking to his mother.",
    C: "He invented reasons for buying the bike.",
    D: "He spent a lot of time riding a friend’s bike.",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: 'The word "it" in paragraph 5 refer to ______.',
    A: "the bike",
    B: "the helmet",
    C: "his hometown Crieff",
    D: "his desperation",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "What does Ewan mean by saying “venturing further afield” in the last paragraph?",
    A: "taking greater risks",
    B: "becoming more independent",
    C: "travelling to more distant places",
    D: "living somewhere different",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Who, according to the whole passage, was most against Ewan getting a motorbike?",
    A: "his first girlfriend",
    B: "his father",
    C: "his mother",
    D: "his friends",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which of the following means most nearly the same as “contrary” in the first paragraph?",
    A: "Opposite",
    B: "Agreeing",
    C: "Equal",
    D: "Embarrassing",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The word “identify” in paragraph 2 is closest in meaning to _____.",
    A: "name",
    B: "estimate",
    C: "discount",
    D: "encounter",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The word “them” in paragraph 2 refer to _____.",
    A: "companies",
    B: "new job opportunities",
    C: "hardware and software",
    D: "webmasters",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "According to the reading passage, which of the following is true about webmasters?",
    A: "They never work independently.",
    B: "They require a minimal level of expertise.",
    C: "The duties they perform depend on the organization they work for.41",
    D: "They do not support software products.",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "Which of the sentences below best expresses the essential information in the highlighted sentence in the passage? The term “new media” is difficult to define because it encompasses a constantly growing set of new technologies and skills.",
    A: "The term “new media” is hard to state because it covers so much skill and technology.",
    B: "The ever-expanding set of new technology and the knowledge based on that technology make the exact meaning of “new media” difficult to specify.",
    C: "Because it is constantly growing, the skills for “new media” difficult to specify.",
    D: "Because new technology and the skills for that technology are always encompassing more fields, the expression “new media” is impossible to specify.",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "What does “it” in paragraph 4 refer to?",
    A: "Modern technology",
    B: "New media",
    C: "Webmaster’s career",
    D: "The Internet",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "It can be inferred from the passage that ______.",
    A: "online workers can work full-time online.",
    B: "only skilled workers make good money.",
    C: "it is easy to become a webmaster.",
    D: "workers with limited computer skills cannot work online.",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "What is the purpose of this passage?",
    A: "To inform people about the tasks and role of a webmaster",
    B: "To inform people about the computer industry",
    C: "To inform people about employment related to the internet",
    D: "To explain why webmasters make a lot of money",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "According to the passage, all of the following are true EXCEPT ______.",
    A: "there are online jobs available for workers with minimal computer skills.",
    B: "webmasters must have knowledge of the latest computer applications.",
    C: "online workers cannot free themselves from the office.",
    D: "“new media” is not easy to define.",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The word “vary” in paragraph 6 could be best replaced by which of the following?",
    A: "Change",
    B: "Decrease",
    C: "Increase",
    D: "Differ",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The largest country in the North America is _____.",
    A: "The US",
    B: "Canada",
    C: "Greenland",
    D: "Mexico",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "All four seasons can be found in _____.",
    A: "Canada",
    B: "Alaska",
    C: "eastern US",
    D: "Greenland",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "Rain is hardly found in _____.",
    A: "southern California",
    B: "Mexico",
    C: "western interior",
    D: "southern Canada",
    Correct: "A",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "The human geography of the continent was dramatically changed due to _____.",
    A: "the diversified climate",
    B: "the inhabitants of the Mexican heartland",
    C: "the migrations from Europe",
    D: "ethnic people",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "_____ became less and less in number.",
    A: "The Mexican people",
    B: "The Hispanic people",
    C: "the indigenous peoples",
    D: "the French people",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "The main language(s) of the Canadian people is (are) _____.",
    A: "English",
    B: "English and French",
    C: "Spanish",
    D: "Spanish and native American",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "Nowadays, most people in North America have _____ background.",
    A: "Native American",
    B: "Indian",
    C: "European",
    D: "Canadian",
    Correct: "C",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "There are more _____ in the west than in the east of the US.",
    A: "rains",
    B: "seasons",
    C: "precipitations",
    D: "mountains",
    Correct: "D",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question: "_____ has longer winter than other parts of the continent.",
    A: "southern Canada",
    B: "Greenland",
    C: "California",
    D: "Mexico",
    Correct: "B",
  },
  {
    CODE: "CODE 4",
    Question:
      "North America is now the _____ densely populated continent in the world.",
    A: "third",
    B: "fourth",
    C: "14th",
    D: "most",
    Correct: "B",
  },
];

function run(num) {
  const x = data.map((item, id) => {
    return {
      id: String(id + 1),
      code: item.CODE,
      question: item.CODE + ": " + item.Question,
      options: [item.A, item.B, item.C, item.D],
      answer: item.Correct,
    };
  });

  console.log(JSON.stringify(x.filter((item) => item.code === num)));
}
run("CODE1");
run("CODE 2");
run("CODE 3");
run("CODE 4");
